https://icerabath.com/privacy/

Skip to content
Privacy & Cookies
NEED US?CALL US.
855-444-2372
Policy last updated:  December 2019By using this site, you agree with our use of cookies.OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACYIcera LLC and its affiliates (“Icera”) are committed to your privacy. We want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information.  This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information that we collect online and offline.WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as a natural person or relates to an identifiable natural person.  We may collect and process the following Personal Information:Personal contact information such as name, address, telephone number and email address;Business contact information such as business address, telephone number and email address;Information necessary to provide services or products to you;Comments and opinions you provide when you contact us directly by email, telephone or mail;Payment and transaction information for billing purposes.“Other Information” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individual.  We may collect and process the following Other Information:Browser and device information;App usage data;Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies.Demographic information and other information provided by you that does not reveal your specific identity;Information that has been aggregated in a manner such that it no longer reveals your specific identity.If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we will collect, use and disclose it for the purposes for which we collect, use and disclose Personal Information as detailed in this Policy.HOW WE COLLECT PERSONAL AND OTHER INFORMATIONWe and our service providers may collect Personal Information online in a variety of ways in connection with our services or products, including:Through our websites (“Websites”);Through the software applications made available by us for use on or through computers and mobile devices (“Apps”);Through social media properties (“Our Social Media”);Through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy (“Emails”);Through extranet sites made available to our clients and third parties (“Extranet Sites”); andThrough our registration process for newsletters, seminars, webinars and events.We also may collect Personal Information offline in a variety of ways in connection with our, includingWhen you participate in a contractual arrangement for services or products;When you provide information in conjunction with our services or products; orWhen you interact with us at an event.We also may collect Personal Information from other sources, including:Publicly available databases;Joint marketing partners and event sponsors, when they share the information with us;Other entities or franchisees to which we provide products and services;Referral sources; andSocial media platforms.We need to collect Personal Information in order to provide our products and services to you.  If you do not provide the information requested, we may not be able to provide our products or services.  If you disclose any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with our products and services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.USING COOKIESCookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the services, pages visited, language preferences and other traffic data. We do not currently respond to browser do-not-track signals.IP ADDRESSYour IP address is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider.  An IP address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses our systems, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other systems.  We use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels, diagnosing server problems and administering the systems.  We may also derive your approximate location from your IP address.We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law.  In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information.  If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined.THIRD PARTY SERVICESThis Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties.This includes any third party operating any website or service to which our websites may link.  The inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or by our affiliates.In addition, we are not responsible for the information collection, use, disclosure or security policies or practices of other organizations, such as Facebook, Apple, Google, Microsoft, RIM or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider or device manufacturer, including with respect to any Personal Information you disclose to other organizations through or in connection with the Apps or our Social Media.UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYThe “LAST UPDATED” legend at the top of this Privacy Policy indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy.  Your use of our online services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.
Scroll to Top
